Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Immortal Team @Viki
So, if that sword is removed
Ajusshi will disappear,
from this world, completely?
End the goblin's immortality
and make him cease to exist.
That is the Goblin's Bride's fate.
Even you almost killed her once
with your own hands.
It's moving
The moment you pull the sword out
he will go to be dust and wind.
This world... to another
world somewhere, forever.
This is not your fault
Miscellaneous Omitted Person.
If you are thinking that we are accomplices
or on the same side, then I feel wronged.
The one who did not say was Kim
Shin and I just replies sincerely.
And this moment that I am talking
to you, I am on your side.
Thank you for telling me. Please rest.
This place too...
was not my home either.
This lifetime
I must not have a home.
Let's go Buckwheat. Let's go.
Episode 9
Han Mi Stationary Store
Excuse me.
It's been a long time. Would
you like to have a drink?
I am so angry right now.
Alcohol... will you be buying?
I don't have a card these days.
I, who have lived a hundred years.
On a day that's just right
it was first love.
So that I could confess. So
that the heavens would permit
I am asking.
The last word you leave is?
All the time I have spent with you
were all blindingly bright.
Because the day was good,
because the day was not good
because the day was just right.
All the days were good.
And also, whatever happens...
It is not your fault.
That was a parting greeting?
Seriously... should I kill you?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Immortal Team @Viki
That day Miscellaneous Omitted Person...
walked for a long time in someone's tears.
If possible, for the Goblin's
death to be as far as possible
She's not here. She hasn't come
back and I can't call her.
I think she ran away.
That is...
Her bags are not here and even Mr.
Buckwheat.
That is...
What is Mr. Buckwheat?
Sh'es not on the beach too.
She didn't go to school either.
She's not near the door in the library that
she followed me through Canada through.
Not even near the park where she
summoned me the second time.
The ghost who has seen Ji Eun Tak.
Where is that store that you
always bought chicken from?
The chicken store that Ji Eun Tak works.
Even the ghosts don't know her whereabouts.
You bring this along with you?
I thought you would be looking for her.
The true culprit is me.
I told her everything.
What?
Did you perhaps?
Yeah. If she pulls out
the sword you would die.
I told her everything.
Are you crazy? Why would you tell her?
You told me never to tell her!
I did... but this time,
as expected I am on the
same side with Miscellaneous
Omitted Person.
What kind of meddling is that? On
what are you on the same side?
You dying... I don't want that.
There's no other meaning to that.
It's just that if you return to
nothingness, it would be boring.
You can get mad.
How could I get mad? How?
The one who wants me to die
is telling me not to die.
I get no guarantee on getting
pickled radishes either.
If you would refrain from using those
coupons, then I would be thank-
Oh no... a friendship really formed.
Looking for a part-time worker.
Don't contact me from now on.
Don't greet me even if we meet.
Happy New Year.
Olive Chicken
Orabeoni (BIG BROTHER).
Why are you looking into my store?
Perhaps... are you applying
for a part-time job?
That's not it. I am in the middle of
searching for the part-time worker here.
2500?
Clothes, watch, shoes. From head to
toe, you are dressed in a total of 2500
what would a person like
that need to be looking
for my part-time worker
who earns 6300 won?
Perhaps is the one who made her cry, you?
Are you him who made her conscious while
eating and works for the country?
Did she cry?
So it's you. The one who
cut my part-time worker.
This is totally adding up to me.
Are you perhaps a married man? Is that
why you just let her go like that?
I'm not married but I have a bride
so your judgment isn't wrong.
Then, let's meet again.
I think the complicated ill
fate is not only with me.
Look here.
Look here! Orabeoni (BIG BROTHER)!
You didn't find her?
You said you didn't turn in Eun Tak's
papers, right? Turn the papers in for now.
What documents?
Miscellaneous Omitted Person documents.
The documents need to be there for
the date of her death to be set.
You are hoping for the child to die are you!
I need to know where or how she
would die for you or me to go.
What do you mean?
Why would Miscellaneous Omitted Person die?
I don't even have the desire.
There must be another reason.
What on earth are we?
How could both a Goblin and Grim Reaper be
together but can't even save one child.
I will get the documents.
But then... during that while,
what if something happens?
Go and come back. If something happens,
I would be able to feel something.
If at that crucial moment the person that
she would be looking for is me, that is.
These are the documents for
Miscellaneous Omitted Person.
Process it as fast as possible.
It's an urgent one.
Tomorrow afternoon.
That's late.
Today afternoon.
Miscellaneous Omitted Person Application
Ji Eun Tak?
Isn't she the one, whose name you
were looking for at the bus station?
Who is she?
Goblin's bride.
What? This person... really?
Ah, so is that why the
Goblin was there that time?
Get your sandwich, eat it,
while eating it realise
"Ah, my flattery was excessive.
Let's shut up." Start.
Okay.
Those people don't live here,
they moved out a long time ago.
Aigoo, what a nuisance. How
much debt do they owe?
Sorry.
Where does this girl live?
Why are you looking for Ji Eun Tak?
Her exam results arrived,
but Eun Tak doesn't
come to school anymore,
I'm the class president.
Ajusshi, who are you? How
do you know Ji Eun Tak?
(I KNOW HER) well.
I'll hand this to her. Well.
2017 College Entrance Exam Scorecard
This... what?
Is these grades good or what?
What?
Ah... yes. With those grades, you
can get into a college in Seoul
I'm quite proud.
2017 College Entrance Exam Scorecard
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Immortal Team @Viki
How can she said that's not her mom?
You think it doesn't exist?
What do you want? Sorry.
I'm not in my right mind right now. You take
these. Grim Reaper must need to buy socks.
Breaking news. The bodies of
skyscrapers have been covered
in thick fog. Only the tops of
the building's are visible.
The incessant fog is also mystic
as if it's something divine.
Breaking news.
This scene that appears to be from a Sci-Fi
film, is the night sky of Seoul today.
Between the buildings the
super moon is shinning high.
With the giant fog and the
purple moon now...
The citizens cannot hide their concern.
Quickly draw out that sword.
Draw that sword, and go into nothingness.
If you don't go into
nothingness, Eun Tak will die.
If I... make that choice,
you have to be ready with an excuse.
Father.
8:15.
The patient has passed away.
Father! Father!
Kim Ki Joong, 68 years old. Cause
of death, excessive blood loss.
Ah, hot!
Father?
A-
Oh! Father, did you come back alive,
father? You lost so much blood. This is...
Did you get up?
In front of my eyes, he just
woke up, he's alive. He
had excessive blood loss, but
he body colour was good.
The list of names just burned up.
Is this a possible event?
It is possible, if that's the Goblin's fire.
This must be yours.
What is this?
The Goblin's apology.
Apology?
It's socks...
Is apologising in advance enough?
You caused the trouble, so why does
the Grim Reaper have to do the overtime?
How dare you burn our list?
Has living forever made you go blind?
You two's tragic fate is unfortunate...
but that doesn't mean you can meddle with
a human's life, you senseless goblin!
I just... wanted someone to see it.
It would be good if the deity saw it.
It would be better if Eun Tak saw it.
If you say it like that,
what does that make me?
I shouldn't have said anything.
I should've just let the Miscellaneous
Omitted Person pull out the sword.
You're right. That would've been better.
In this world...
there are many weird beings that
are unexplainable with words.
At times, they're closer
to us than we think.
I think, that you already had an idea.
Yoo Jae Shin.
Sorry.
Eh-hey!
One man who doesn't age, I know one.
Okay...
The passport I made and
accommodations, I prepared
in Nice and making me stay
by Deok Hwa's side...
I believe that you gave me these
jobs to recognise on my own.
Have you by chance spoke of
that existence anywhere?
There is none.
Actually, he is the one who picked you.
He made a child without a dream and money,
take the entrance exam, gave him a dream,
enrolled him in a university, who do
you think is that faceless helper?
Remember. The person's real name is...
Kim-to, Shin-believe.
Hey, Kim Shin. The supermoon and
the fog, was you right, uncle?
No.. why are you creating such a
mess to find a high school girl?
I'm really scared that NASA
would actually take you away.
Did you drink alcohol?
Yesterday, I drank.
Now, I'm sober.
Anyways, if I do find
her, what would you do
for me, uncle? Will you
give me a credit card?
If I cant find her, how will you?
She wouldn't have gone far. She
has no money. She has to be
somewhere in Korea where you can go by bus.
I have my ways..
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Immortal Team @Viki
Please wait a moment.
Hello.
Yes, wait a moment, please.
Wait a moment. Yes.
[NEWS ALERTS]
I found her. Right now,
she's at a ski resort.
What if...
I say I don't want to be your
bride anymore, what will happen?
Ah...
This sword won't be pulled out.
Only you can do it.
The sword needs to be pulled out...
I...
to become pretty. Right now, I'm not pretty.
You don't know, but I'm crazy
for laughing in this situation.
Crazy person.
Not today, today I'll just laugh with you.
When the first show comes?
First snow?
You don't need a broom then.
When the first snow comes.
There's a lot of snow.
Let's go home.
You shouldn't stay here alone.
I don't have a house.
None of the places I thought were
my home, was actually my home.
People just kept me close, for
some because of insurance.
And for some because they wanted to die.
I now understand it all, I'm the tool
to end the goblin's immortality, I am?
I missed the opportunity to tell you.
Because I missed the
opportunity, I was glad.
If possible, until the moment of death
I was about to lose every opportunity.
But I shouldn't do that.
The blood of thousands is on this sword.
The weight of a person's life
it should not be up to my judgement.
So take this sword out. I ask of you.
No.
I don't want to. I don't
want to even if I die.
So don't look for me. Don't look for me
and let's live as separate people
who don't know each other.
Go far from me,
and live for a very very long time, Mr.
Kim Shin.
Do you understand?
Don't appear again.
If you appear in front of my eyes again,
then I will really kill you then.
♫ Hold my ♫
♫ Aching heart ♫
♫ Just like this ♫
♫ It's cold ♫
♫ I'm standing underneath ♫
♫ A sky colder than winter ♫
♫ Even my tears are frozen ♫
♫ Quietly call me who's hurting ♫
♫ My name no matter how ♫
♫ Defying the everlasting
and just for a day ♫
♫ No, even if it's just for a minute ♫
♫ If it's possible, I'll endure it ♫
♫ If at the end of my wait, you are ♫
♫ Standing there ♫
♫ Memories of you ♫
♫ That were like a painting ♫
♫ A day that was like a present ♫
♫ I was longing for ♫
♫ Crossing over the long lasting time ♫
♫ Coming to me ♫
You took the exam well.
You call this an excuse.
I was happy to have this as an excuse.
Even like this,
an excuse that I can come see you.
What do you want to do after seeing me?
What do you plan to do
after getting that excuse?
Live together or die together?
If you appear before me again,
did I tell you that I would kill you or not?
Fine, come here.
I will pull out the sword.
If that is your wish so bad then
I will pull it out for you.
Come here now.
This man, til the end.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Immortal Team @Viki
Don't.
Do it. You have to do it.
Let go! Let go!
Let go! Let go, I said!
It was from that moment.
In the hotel, when you appeared
it was from that moment.
Ahjussi, do you love me?
If that is needed then that too.
♫ And I'm here ♫
I love you.
So... did you really love me?
No?
You didn't even just a bit?
I was scared.
I'm so scared.
So, you keep...
I wished you would keep needing me.
I wish I could do even that.
That excuse to get permission
I wish I would have it.
With that excuse, I...
I wish I could stay alive.
With you.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Immortal Team @Viki
♫ I'll be here ♫
♫ For you ♫
♫ If I could fly above the clouds ♫
♫ Like all the birds ♫
♫ I could hold you for a while ♫
♫ To let you feel my pulse ♫
♫ Do you hear ♫
♫ all of those ♫
Hello. It's the customer's personal errand.
Edge waxing.
He's asking to have it done within one hour.
Why isn't Chief Kim coming?
I'm rotating right now so
he will probably come.
Let's wait. - Yes.
Why are you alone? What about
Miscellaneous Omitted Person?
You didn't meet her? - I met her.
But she's not coming. -
What on earth happened?
It's my first time waiting for
a document to be processed.
Miscellaneous Omitted Person's roll is out.
Are you sure it's Eun Tak's?
It's empty. - There is writing.
What on earth is this situation?
It was as if someone pushed for her death.
That's not me.
And all the more not you. - It must be me.
I have to die for her to live.
If I live then she dies.
That is the fate of that child and me.
This is the punishment
that was bestowed to me.
God had a greater reason.
Don't say something so weak.
Even if it was God's will
but it is not mine.
You will also be the same.
One hour from now, the time of death.
You should hurry.
The phone is turned off.
This person is not able to
be reached at this time.
Death will constantly
come before that child.
She probably has encountered
it several times.
She will face more in the future.
More times than the accidents
now and more severe.
It's the first snow, Mister!
But why is the first snow so early?
It's so fascinating.
I wish you would continue to need me.
I wish you would ask that of me.
I wish I could use
permission as an excuse.
I need you.
That's all I ask of you.
I love you.
♫ See you never gone away ♫
♫ It will be better someday ♫
♫ Never far away ♫
Ji Eun Tak. Have you come to your senses?
This is the hospital.
You showed symptoms of
hypothermia and concussion.
It's a relief that you're okay.
If you were even a little
bit late, your condition
would've become dangerous.
Ah.
How long have I been in this state?
A day and a half.
Ah.
Then, what about the hospital fee?
Ah. You don't need to worry about that.
But, what is your relationship
with the CEO of Cheonho Group?
The Chairman himself came
in to admit you into the
hospital. The entire
hospital was in an uproar.
If you want, you can be discharged.
I recommend staying here for your safety...
I'm sorry, but
by chance, does anyone
have a match or lighter...
Pardon?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Immortal Team @Viki
♫ How can I care for you ♫
♫ Please touch my heart just once ♫
♫ It feels so cold ♫
♫ I'm standing underneath ♫
♫ A sky colder than winter ♫
♫ My tears are frozen ♫
♫ Quietly call me who's hurting ♫
♫ My name that you have
called many times ♫
♫ Going back eternity to see you one day ♫
♫ No, even if I get to
see you for a minute ♫
♫ If I can do that, I will endure it ♫
♫ If you are standing at
the end of my long wait ♫
♫ Memories of you that seemed like ♫
♫ a painting ♫
♫ A day that is like a present
that I was longing for ♫
♫ Crossing over such a long time ♫
♫ I will wait ♫
♫ You who was the first snow in my heart ♫
♫ I will always ♫
You should've told me you were leaving...
I thought you weren't coming back so I...
I came early and waited.
Who told you to come early? You should
come when I blow out the candle.
You should've come there. You should've
appeared in front of my eyes.
I came here to hold your hand.
I don't know. Whatever.
Me, too.
What?
If you don't know, never mind.
I know it though.
Then that's good.
I... have something to confess.
I can't see anything else about you, Mister.
You're tall, your clothes look
expensive, and your eyes are amazing.
That's all I see. So,
I can't pull out the sword for you anymore.
I won't pull it out, even if you smile.
In my eyes,
you're still really pretty.
♫ It's a beautiful life ♫
♫ I’ll be by your side ♫
♫ I’ll stand behind you ♫
♫ It's a beautiful life ♫ ♫ Beautiful day ♫
♫ I would live in your memory ♫
♫ Beautiful life ♫ ♫ Beautiful day ♫
♫ Stay with me ♫
♫ Beautiful my love ♫ ♫
Beautiful your heart ♫
♫ It's a beautiful life ♫
♫ Beautiful life ♫
His face is pale white and his lips are red.
He has black clothes.
And is holding a black hat.
Oh my.
What is it? Why?
By chance, did you exchange your names?
He's the Grim Reaper.
What did I tell you? I told you to
be careful of men with black hats!
Do you make enough money to eat? Do you
have any other customers besides me?
This woman, if you're wary
of men, you can't date!
Grim Reaper? You have to be believable
if you want to write me a talisman.
Then who is this man? He's very tall.
He seems a little older than me and
looks kind of like Gong Yoo...
His voice... if you listen
to him, you feel as
though you're at the smallest
cafe in the world...
Gong Yoo?
Then stay well.
Did you receive a sparkling
item from somewhere?
- How did you know that?
- Throw it away.
You can't take things whose
previous owners are unknown.
You don't know what's inside. There might
be the owner's crimes, sins, desires, etc.
What crimes, what sins,
and what desires would be inside this?
I'm sorry. I didn't mean
to cause you trouble.
I always have to contact him first.
Right now?
Aish.
- Are you busy? - Yes. I'm
so busy, I'm going insane.
What are you doing right now?
I'm trying to figure out my passcode.
I want to
turn it off, ust in case
it makes another sound.
The passcode failed. Try
again in one minute.
(WHAT ARE YOU DOING NOW?)
(WHY AREN'T YOU TRYING TO CONTACT ME AGAIN?)
Oh... That's...
Firstly, because I feel sorry about
having erased your memory. Secondly,
Who are you, and why are you so beautiful?
I thought I started to have
a crush on someone else.
I'm sorry. I am also feeling very
confused about myself for being this way.
It seems like you've gotten a message.
I miss you.
- Me too.
- Why am I constantly like this...
No, I haven't heard anything.
I didn't hear anything, I didn't
hear anything, I didn't...
Glory, glory, glory, hallelujah
I know that you're there!
Come out and show yourself!
How dare a lowly ghost is
trying to harm a human being?
Come out, not get out! Get lost!
If you don't obey me,
I'll sing the song again!
Glory, glory, glory, hallelujah
Glory! Glory! Hallelujah.
Why are you empty-handed? What about your
luggage? Weren't you on your way home?
No, I was on heading to my workplace.
Since it's Christmas season, they pay
really well. I'm glad I didn't get fired.
Let's finish up what we're
supposed to do. Then,
let's buy some beef
and go to Geumweewon.
Until when? Until when are
you going to be here?
What do you mean by until when? Until all
of February's snow at the ski resort melt.
You can go back home first.
What? February?!
President Yu. Yes, President Yu, it's me.
I was going to ask you to fire
someone using your vast network.
Otherwise, I'm planning to
quickly melt all the snow
at the ski resort. Which
option shall I go for?
I'm back.
I'm sorry. You would have worried a lot.
I worred a little, this
guy's the one who worried a
lot. / The one who found out
about you was Deok Hwa.
And the one who got you here is me.
It's the first time to have a place
to return to, so I'm feeling weird.
It feels like this place
is now really my home.
This girl's starting again...
You have a sad story
to tell each time I ask
you about something!
I'd feel afraid to ask
you to come back home.
Just wear it. You should come with me.
Where are you going to take my Ajuhshi?
That's something I feel sensitive about.
'my'... she said 'my' Ajuhshi...!!
I can hear everything, you cheesy Goblin!
He said he was happy that you
referred to him with the pronoun "my"
Follow me quickly! Leave that soup there!
Btw, who are you submitting this report to?
Are you submitting it directly to...?
It doesn't get handed in to that far up.
They probably created
our jobs because they didn't want
to read all of those reports.
I think they should be of
the same handwriting though
I'll say that it's been written with my
left hand, so just shut up and write!
Btw she seemed pretty - the ownder of the
chicken restaurant you visit frequently
You met her? You didn't tell her
anything useless by any chance, did you?
What I told her wasn't something
that was particularly useful.
You told her? That I was a Reaper?
You told her too! That I would disappear
to nothing once the sword gets pulled out.
Did you really tell her? Really?
Wow, how can you...?
You... really... you / Ohhh how...
How... how... someone's
coming in, coming in!
Hey there, I'm really sorry, but it's
an emergency... Could I use the toilet?
This is a human being, right?
It's not an immortal for sure... But
human beings cannot enter this place!
Wow
Please... What should I do...
It's urgent!! AAA!!!
Thank you, thank you. It's really urgent.
Wow... There is no door that a human
being's desperation can't open.
I can't believe it even after witnessing it.
You even believe in God
that's not visible. Then, why
can't you believe a human
being, which is visible?
That's called the persistency
of a human being. The power
that enables them to change
their destiny on their own!
How can an immortal's tea-place be
a human being's mark of territory?
How can I write an explanation
report for this case...!
Sit.
Write this one too, it
happened because of you!
You can make Deok Hwa do
it when you get home.
Hiring
Do you have a boyfriend?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Immortal Team @Viki
I am Ji Eun Tak.
I lost my parents at age nine and...
You can ask me about anything
that you're curious about.
FYI, I can adjust myself so that I
can satisfy all your requirements.
Do you have any plan later on?
No. / Then, today is our
official first day together.
You can work here.
Yes! I'll take care of
everything very methodically!
Btw, how did you come to a better place?
Life has very simple explanations.
I returned my apartment-on-lease.
How did you find me here without
even calling me beforehand?
I have my own means.
Even ghosts would be surprised.
Are you a beggar? How can an
elementary student not even have $1?
You guys don't have money either!!
That's why I'm telling you to bring it.
Then, we would have it.
Don't hit me! Strong wind!!
This kid must be crazy.
He said 'strong wind.'
Your mom ran away since you
read comic books all the time.
Hey! You guys are being so
cowardly despite being males!
Come here, come and get hit yourselves too!
Let's go, let's go.
Are you ok?
Someday, you'll be able to shoot a real
strong wind. Where's your home? Is it near?
The results would have come out already...
ohh..ohh What should I do
I don't know.
Oh noo
Ooohh
Ohhh no oh no
Now, let's print out the
tuition request form!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Immortal Team @Viki
I'm not joking, someone
else paid for your tuition.
He told me to mention his name, Shin Kim,
if you ever call me for confirmation.
Mr. Shin Kim? You paid my tuition?
Hey...
I beseeched them to keep it secret.
According to her, you asked her to make sure
to let me know that you had paid it for me.
She insisted on knowing my name,
so I couldn't help but tell her
According to her, she kept
asking you about the name
of the student, but you
kept telling her your name.
I'm not sure if this would be an
appropriate university acceptance gift.
This pretty bag...
It's appropriate! Wow that's great, wow!
It's appropriate!
I knew it would be appropriate.
Congratulations!
I really missed you! A
purse, perfume, five...
There's no 5 million won. I
paid your tuition with that.
Ahjussi...
Don't be too moved. I'm lending it to you.
I know... why did you give it to me at
first, but you're lending it to me now?
How could a person's heart change?
You're the only mortal in this house.
How can you not know that yet?
- Daebak...
- 5208 won per month...
Pay it over 80 years. You
can't miss even a month.
80 years?
Yeah, you can't pay back sooner either.
- What? You don't like it?
- No.
If you're so determined like this, I
made up my mind. I set my mind to it.
About what?
A date.
Dummy... when I was at the ski
resort, not my report card...
If you had brought this purse, I
would've came back with you right away.
Wow... that's exactly
what I was going to do.
- The Grim Reaper ahjussi stopped you, huh?
- Yeah!
As expected... the Grim Reaper
ahjussi saved someone's life.
Or I would've killed you on the spot.
Don't eat mine. Eat yours.
I ate all of mine.
- Don't smile and keep eating.
- Just one bite.
- But you know...
- What now?
Do these things have love
out there somewhere?
Look carefully. I tried my
best to put them in there.
Here is the list of gifts
you asked for that
female highschooler or
college students prefer.
BTS?
What do these boys do?
♫ Why do you make my heart waver?
Make my heart waver? ♫
Oh... they work to change people's hearts.
They're wavering people's
hearts quite a bit these days.
EXO? Is that an alcoholic beverage?
No, it's not.
♫ Growl, growl, growl. ♫
Being an executive assistant
is an extreme job. Yeah...
I enjoy my job very much.
I'll choose number three for the gift.
Oh...
I know what digital camera is.
Dear Ji Eun Tak, you worked hard.
I hope each moment is remembered forever.
From Yoo Shin Woo
- Oh, you scared me!
- Aigoo, he scared me.
Since when were you standing here?
Why are you so shocked? Did
you do something wrong?
I was surprised by my face.
I'm handsome, huh? I'm too much...
too much...
You said you don't even have any money.
What's with the camera?
Ah, it's yours.
Why is that mine?
A gift from my grandpa. My
selfie if my gift to you.
Really?
I'm so touched.
The only gift I ever
received was a building. You
must be so happy to
receive a digital camera.
Please tell the Chairman
I'm so, so grateful.
Please give me my camera.
Give me ten minutes.
- Give it back.
- Five minutes.
- Give it back - Fi-, Five Minuites.
Ah, give it!
Three minutes.
Give it now!
Give it!
Three, Three. Oh it's the goblin!
If there's kids in a house, it
really does make the house livelier.
I would've told you if I did.
Anyway I was curious. What will you do now?
Do you remember that man who barged
into your tea room, one time?
How could I forget him? But why?
A human's desperation can open any door.
Maybe that one door opens in a way, that
could be a variable in the deity's plan.
So I plan to start searching, desperately.
What door do I need to open,
to change the deity's plans?
It might take 100 years, or
10 months, I don't know, but
for now I have decided to
stay by that child's side.
And then I might be able to open a door.
I just hope it's not the room to my door.
But why would a deity be
involved in a human's passings.
Why is the reason for the deity to do that?
I was feeling reay touched right then.
Uncles!
Me too! Me too!
Me too, me too, me too!
Now... are you ready to take it?
Why are you here? Just the two...
I don't want to! I sat here first.
I'm going to take it.
Ah.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Immortal Team @Viki
I have a question, I'll move if you answer.
Ah, what is it now?
Backing out suddenly
while driving, solving
math problems writing
with mechanical pencil...
Smiling when she talks.
Keeping off the roads away from the cars
Our boss, you'll never know what she wants.
Be ready for anything.
What are you doing since then?
After calling 100 times...
It's dangerous, so I want you to
walk on the inside of the pavement.
By acting that awkwardly?
You had something to say, so say
it first since I'm curious.
I have no religion.
What?
Why does he talk so well?
By any chance, do you have a religion?
Where you still thinking
about that until now?
I didn't get to tell you last time.
Why have you been smiling so much since?
Me? What? Does my makeup look weird?
Don't you think I'm cute?
Where? Why didn't you meet me on Christmas?
You would have been cute that if you
came that day. What did you do?
You wouldn't have a gone to a church.
Christmas is a bit... you know.
It's someone's birthday, it would
be wrong to go against it.
But, I said I have no religion, do
you seriously think I'm not cute?
Ah, goosebumps...
Did you have to go that far?
No, it's deja vu.
I remember this from before.
It's so fresh in my mind.
Ah, I got goosebumps!
You didn't have to walk me.
Why are you telling me that
now that we're already here?
See you.
Oh! It's the grim reaper!
Most of our sales come from that
person's pocket. Unlike someone else...
How much is fried chicken? I
could buy the whole shop.
Eh... you're scared of chicken
blood, I read up all on goblins.
I'm not scared of it, I just
like to keep a distance from it.
Wait... Is that why you got me a job
at chicken shop in the first place?
To keep away from me?
Ah, that was a while ago...
So it's true? Is that what you wanted,
I didn't even know that. Enough now...
I know so you can go now.
I will live over there
for 1000 years, don't
come looking for me
Coward!
What? What did you say to me?
Ah, It's the first time I've heard that been
said. It's really my first time, really!
Before people would say to me, 'Hooray!'
Shall I show you how brave I am?
Where are you going?
Our boss isn't like most other women.
By any chance is he the
man giving you trouble?
They can hear all.
You don't know my voice. It's isn't that
person's voice, that phone call from then?
They can hear all, shut up!
Is that so?
We meet again, I didn't know
that you two were friends...
He came to the old shop looking for you.
Ah, I see...
How much did you say? Not much.
Yeah, he didn't. So I still
don't know who he is.
Excuse me, but how old are you?
Don't ask if your excusing.
That's how you evade my question, huh?
I'm not evading. I'm flat
out denying to answer you.
You're words are so rude! Why?
Why is it?
I'm much older than I look,
I'm a quite complicated man.
Now, now... if you have
had enough, please
leave. It's a time when
we get many customers.
I still haven't eaten yet.
No, you've eaten all. Now
please just go home.
Because of you things have gone weird!
Customer, you should both leave together.
Get up both of you, quickly!
No!
Let's see. What is X? What's X?
What are you doing?
You really don't know a lot about women.
It doesn't look like you know the answer.
Just drink your beer.
Excuse me, Kim Sun.
Two beers over here please.
Who?
Two beers.
Can I talk to you for a moment.
Outside, in private!
Ah, okay.
What!
What was what?
Just now, you called me Kim Sun.
What about that?
How do you know my name?
I'm sure that I never told you my real name.
Sorry, we didn't meet
How do you know it? Why do you know it?
I said Kim Sunny.
It very cold right? I'll get your coat.
I haven't finished talking.
What is this?
Something went wrong.
Maybe, it started with you,
that's what it seems like.
What's the matter?
Why exactly?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Immortal Team @Viki
♫ When I look at you ♫
♫ I don't know why I keep crying ♫
♫ Were you circling
around coming toward me? ♫
♫ The love that couldn't be avoided ♫
♫ I love you ♫
♫ Love you, love you ♫
The woman in the painting
is Kim Shin's sister.
This ring... what did you mean by it?
♫ And I miss you ♫
When I saw the woman in
the painting, I cried.
♫ My fate, my love ♫
This world beneathe my emperor...
That emperor... beneathe my feet...
You!
You, bitch!
I will uphold your command.
Do you even know what you're asking for?
♫ I felt that we were meant to be ♫
You must come visit me often.
Do you even know who this guy
is that you're seeing him?
Are you the Grim Reaper?
I was contemplating whether I should
hold your hand once more or not, Sunny.
Then, can you hold it today?
When I'm a year younger?
The history between those two...
Is it relevant to my forgotten memory?
Yes, looks to be that way.
♫ Let us not part ♫
♫ Please don't leave my side ♫